sonyericsson.net 2018-11-20

# Sony Mobile Privacy Policy - Sony Mobile (Global English)

**Are there any local or regional differences to Sony Mobile’s personal data handling?**

  1. **A. California Residents Privacy Rights Notice**

California residents have the right to receive: a) information identifying any third party company(ies) to whom Sony Mobile may have disclosed, within the past year, personal data pertaining to you related to direct marketing purposes; and b) a description of the categories of the personal data disclosed. Please email your request to us using the details provided in section 13 below. 

  1. **B. Notice for Australia Residents**

In relation to Section 5 “International transfers of your personal data” above, we will disclose your personal data to parties in a number of countries, including Singapore, New Zealand, the United States of America, Japan, the United Kingdom, Sweden, Ireland and Belgium. From time to time we will need to disclose your personal data to parties in other countries not on this list. This will be on an ad hoc or case by case basis and for the purposes for which we collected your personal data. **Complaints** : If you are concerned that we have not complied with your legal rights or applicable privacy laws, you may bring a complaint internally through our complaints process or you may decide to make a formal complaint with the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner (www.oaic.gov.au) (which is the regulator responsible for privacy in Australia). We will deal with complaints as follows: 

  * **Step 1: let us know**

If you would like to make a complaint, let us know by contacting our PIM Officer at [Australia.privacy.sonymobile@sony.com](mailto:Australia.privacy.sonymobile@sony.com) or use the details set out in section 13 [Contact Us](https://support.sonymobile.com/contactUs/) below.

  * **Step 2: investigation of complaint**

Your complaint will be investigated by our PIM Officer. A response to your complaint will be given in writing within a reasonable period.

  * **Step 3: contact OAIC**

We expect that our procedures will deal fairly and promptly with your complaint. However, if you remain dissatisfied, you can also contact the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner as follows:

  * _Office of the Australian Information Commissioner (OAIC)_
  * _Complaints must be made in writing_
  * _Tel: 1300 363 992_
  * _Address: Director of Compliance_

_Office of the Australian Information Commissioner_

_GPO Box 5218_

_Sydney NSW 2001_

  * Web: [oaic.gov.au](http://www.oaic.gov.au/)

  1. **C. Notice for New Zealand Residents**

Nothing herein shall limit the rights of customers under the Privacy Act 1993. All instructions regarding your data and queries from you will be followed up and answered by us as soon as possible. 

  1. **D. Notice for Malaysia Residents**

In view of the implementation of the Personal Data Protection Act 2010 (“Act”), Sony Mobile recognises the need to process all personal data obtained in a lawful and appropriate manner. The legal responsibility for compliance with the Act lies with Sony Mobile, which is the “data user” under the Act. Compliance with this Privacy Policy and the Act is the responsibility of all employees of Sony Mobile. As and when Sony Mobile is required to collect personal data, Sony Mobile and its employees must abide by the requirements of this Privacy Policy and the Act. In the context of the Act, “processing” is defined as including the collection, recording, holding or storing of personal data which includes, inter alia, NRIC numbers, home address and contact details. A data subject has the following rights under the Act: 

  * Request for access to personal data held on the individual, the purpose for which the personal data is being used and those to whom it has, or can be disclosed;
  * Prevent data processing that is likely to cause distress or damage;
  * Take reasonable action to stop the use of, rectify, erase and/or dispose of inaccurate personal data; and
  * Withdraw consent given to Sony Mobile.

Any individual who intends to exercise the abovementioned rights or has any enquiries regarding this Privacy Policy should make a written request to Sony Mobile at [Malaysia.privacy.sonymobile@sony.com](mailto:Malaysia.privacy.sonymobile@sony.com) or use the details set out in section 13 [Contact Us](https://support.sonymobile.com/contactUs/) below. Sony Mobile will generally be able to respond to such queries and/or requests within 30 days. 

  1. **E. Notice for Singapore Residents**

Sony Mobile collects, uses, discloses, manages and handles Personal Data that is subject to the Personal Data Protection Act 2012 (No. 26 of 2012) (“the Act”). Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. By accessing our website, using any services provided by Sony, signing up for any products and services provided by Sony, submitting any information to us or otherwise showing your agreement thereon, you will be deemed to have agreed and consented to the terms of this Data Protection Policy. “Personal Data” means any data, whether true or false, which can be related to a specific identifiable individual, whether such individual is identifiable from the data itself, or from other information that is available to Sony Mobile. Personal Data includes the personal data collected, used, disclosed, managed and handled in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you (a) have any questions or feedback relating to your Personal Data or our Privacy Policy, (b) would like to withdraw your consent to any use of your Personal Data as set out in this Privacy Policy or otherwise or (c) would like to gain access or make corrections to your Personal Data records, please contact Sony Mobile as follows: 

  * Email: [Singapore.privacy.sonymobile@sony.com](mailto:Singapore.privacy.sonymobile@sony.com)
  * Write in: Data Protection Officer

Sony Mobile Communications International AB, Singapore Branch 2 International Business Park, #01-10 Tower One, The Strategy Singapore 609930 Sony Mobile will generally be able to respond to such queries and/or requests within 30 days. If you withdraw your consent to any or all use of your Personal Data, depending on the nature of your request, Sony Mobile may not be able to continue to provide its products and/or services to you.
